[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 43?",
      "correctAnswer": "1849",
      "options": [
        "1851",
        "1849",
        "1854",
        "1847"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 34?",
      "correctAnswer": "1156",
      "options": [
        "1161",
        "1158",
        "1154",
        "1156"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 23?",
      "correctAnswer": "529",
      "options": [
        "534",
        "527",
        "529",
        "531"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "256",
      "options": [
        "256",
        "254",
        "258",
        "261"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 11?",
      "correctAnswer": "121",
      "options": [
        "119",
        "121",
        "123",
        "126"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "64",
      "options": [
        "62",
        "64",
        "69",
        "66"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "100",
      "options": [
        "100",
        "102",
        "98",
        "105"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "441",
      "options": [
        "441",
        "439",
        "446",
        "443"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 16?",
      "correctAnswer": "256",
      "options": [
        "256",
        "258",
        "254",
        "261"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a square with<br> side length 40?",
      "correctAnswer": "1600",
      "options": [
        "1605",
        "1598",
        "1602",
        "1600"
      ]
    }
]